l_20221023 =[
    {"question":"鶴立雞群","Answer":"hèlì jīqún"},
    {"question":"諺語","Answer":"yànyǔ"},
    {"question":"熱潮","Answer":"rècháo"},
    {"question":"雨後春筍","Answer":"yǔhòuchūnsǔn"},
    {"question":"發揮","Answer":"fāhuī"},
    {"question":"非凡","Answer":"fēifán"},
    {"question":"吐司","Answer":"tǔsī"},
    {"question":"魚丸","Answer":"yúwán"},
    {"question":"蚯蚓","Answer":"qiūyǐn"},
    {"question":"偶爾","Answer":"ǒuěr"},
    {"question":"不屑一顧","Answer":"bùxiè yīgù"},
    {"question":"熱潮","Answer":"rècháo"},
    {"question":"特殊","Answer":"tèshū"},
    {"question":"喜好","Answer":"xǐhào"},
    {"question":"剩飯","Answer":"shèngfàn"},
    {"question":"特製","Answer":"tè zhì"},
    {"question":"凹槽","Answer":"āocáo"},
    {"question":"叩","Answer":"kòu"},
    {"question":"爭相","Answer":"zhēngxiāng"},
    {"question":"特殊","Answer":"tèshū"},
    {"question":"高麗菜葉","Answer":"gāolícài yè"},
    {"question":"挑嘴","Answer":"tiǎozuǐ"},
    {"question":"快高長大","Answer":"kuàigāocháng dà"},
    {"question":"提不起勁","Answer":"tíbùqǐ jìn"},
    {"question":"戲","Answer":"xì"}
]